声明: 本字幕由YYeTs美剧字幕组原创翻译制作
欢迎访问官方论坛  www.YYeTs.net 在线观看 剧情讨论 学习交流
=====本字幕由以下成员荣誉制作 感谢他们的无私奉献======
翻译：Requiem校对：扣扣
后期：阿胜 双语制作：tamama788 傻瓜都一样
========== 字幕总监制：七色九天 ==========
他去伐木了
He went to get some wood,
-往海边去了  -Carlisle在哪?
-took off on the path to the beach.  -Where's Carlisle?
-跟Claire一起去了  -脚印  三组不同的脚印
-He went after Claire.  -Footprints, three distinct sets
到处都是   看上去好像发生过一场搏斗
all over the place. Looks like there might have been a struggle.
我觉得他们很可能是被带走了
I think they've been taken.
我们得准备一下组织一个搜救队
We need to prepare to organize a search party
-要帮忙吗?  -你想的话  当然了
-Can I help?  -Could use another hand, if you're up for it.
这是个荒岛  你打算怎么
This is a deserted island. How exactly are you gonna
去找他们
find them?
你以前是干什么的  Locke先生?
What do you do in the real world?
我是个...地区监督人
I was a...regional collections supervisor
为一家生产盒子的公司工作
for a box company.
好吧
Yeah, right.
你应该回去了  Bonne 回去吧
You should turn around. Bonne. Head back
那你呢
What about you?
我能照顾好自己
I can take care of myself.
不  我不回去
No. I'm not heading back.
我欣赏你的勇气  可是你应该...
I admire your courage, but you...
我不回去
I'm not heading back.
你们都上哪去了?
Where have you been?
这话什么意思?
What do you mean where have we been?
你和Locke早出晚归
You and Locke leaving before sunrise and coming back after dark
连续四天了
during the last four days.
你们干什么去了
What are you doing out there?
我们在找Claire
Looking for Claire.
我以为已经没有线索了
I thought there was no trail anymore
甚至没有人知道该到哪儿去找
that no one even knew where to look.
一分钟内就要下雨了
It's gonna start raining in one minute.
一分钟
One minute?
误差几秒之内
Give or take a few seconds.
他们还没回来
They aren't back yet.
我肯定他们已经在外边露营了
I'm sure they just made camp for the night.
如果说你哥在岛上跟谁一起最安全的话
If there's anyone on this island your brother's safe with,
那个人就是Locke
it's Locke.
生产盒子的公司教过你怎么预测天气吗?
They teach you how to predict the weather at a box company?
我带了件礼物给你
I brought you a present
谢谢你帮我翻译
for helping me with the translations.
我没办法把他包装一下 所以...
I didn't have a chance to get it gift wrapped, so...
我在废墟里面找到这些
I found these in the wreckage,
而且这对我来说也没用
and I have no use for them personally.
它们刚好合我的尺寸
They're actually my size.
嗯  大了半码  不过我敢肯定
Well, half a size off, but I swear,
这个鬼地方已经让我的脚肿了半码
this place is making my feet swell.
又发现了这个岛的一种神秘力量
Another mysterious force on the island revealed.
嘿  Boone  问你点事  兄弟
Yo, Boone. Question for you, dude.
你和Locke每天都出去打野猪是吧
You and Locke are hunting boar every day, right?
怎么了
What about it?
那很好  但是  呃...
It's cool, except
为什么你们什么都没带回来
how come you're not coming back with any?
我们的盘子里一个星期都没有新鲜野猪肉了  哥们
We haven't had fresh pork on our plate in about a week.
它们可不是圈养起来等着你去吃的
It's not like they're domesticated animals.
也许你们还不够努力吧
Maybe you aren't trying hard enough?
我们已经去打猎了  听见没
We're hunting.
但愿如此  大伙都需要食物
I hope so, 'cause people need food, man.
固体食物
Solid food.
这可不是个游戏  哥们
This isn't a game, man.
真不敢相信上一个球你居然接住了
I can't believe you ran down that last ball.
然后打回来赢了
Then you hit it for a winner.
运气好罢了
Lucky shot.
是吗  希望是运气
Yeah, I wish it was luck.
是我的电话吗?
Is that my phone?
喂
Yeah, hello.
Boone  是我
Boone, it's me.
是我
Yeah.
出什么事了
What's the matter?
嗯  有些事情不太妙
Things aren't so good.
你在哪
Where are you?
滚开 离我远点
Get out of here! Get the hell away from me!
Shannon?
在那别动  不要靠近我
Stay out of here! Get the hell away from me!
-Shannon 出什么事了  -现在不能说
-Shannon What's going on?  -I can't talk.
那好吧  Shannon  等一下
All right, hang on.
告诉我你在哪  我去找你
Just tell me where you are. I'll come get you.
悉尼
Sydney.
澳大利亚
Australia.
离我妹妹远点
Stay away from my sister.
刚才你的语气好象在给我下命令
For a moment, you seemed to be giving me an order.
只是一个友好的建议
It's just a friendly suggestion.
一个建议
A suggestion.
是的  要是我是你的话  我一定会听
Yes, and if I were you, I'd listen.
如果我不听呢?
What if I don't?
Boone!
我在小溪那边找到了新的踪迹
I found some fresh tracks down by the stream.
一会见
I'll see you later.
你知道在哪找我
You know where to find me.
你应该把你和Sayid的分歧暂时放到一边
You need to put aside your differences with Sayid.
他想泡我妹妹
He's hitting on Shannon.
他很有能力
He's very competent.
我们并不想与他为敌
We don't want to make an enemy of him.
我们希望让他站在我们这边
We're gonna want him on our side.
John  人们都在议论
John  People are talking
关于我们每天都在这在做什么
about what we're doing out here every day,
特别是看到我们什么也没带回去
since we never come back with anything.
-你是说没有野猪  -是的
-You mean boar.  -Yeah.
还有很多水果和鱼可以吃啊
plenty of fruit and fish to go around.
我们现在做的事要重要得多
What we're doing here is far more important.
现在
Right now
这才是最优先要做的
this is our priority.
你好 Jack...
So, Jack...
你好  Hurley
So, Hurley.
我有点很重要的事
There's something kind of important
一直想问你
I've been wanting to ask you about.
我所要告诉你的  呃...
Anything I tell you is, uh,
是医生和病人之间的秘密  行吗
doctor-patient confidential, right?
好的
Yeah.
事情是这样的
The thing is,
我有点不舒服
I haven't been feeling so great.
怎么回事啊
What's the matter?
嗯  好像是
Well, it's kinda like, uh,
我的胃
my stomach.
有点消化不良
I've been having some, um...major digestive issues.
你这几天都吃了什么东西
What have you been eating?
和平常一样……
You know, the usual
香蕉  木瓜  芒果...
Bananas, papayas, mangoes,
石榴  西番莲果...
guava, passion fruit,
椰子  还有山上采回来的一些无名水果
coconut, some of those weird star fruits from up on the hill.
有人告诉我说那是帮助消化的
Someone said they'd be good for digestion.
我告诉你吧  他们在撒谎
Let me tell you, they lied.
如果有点蛋白质
It might help if you had a little more protein
在你的食物里的话  可能会有用
in your diet
哥们  我该怎么办
Dude  What can I do?
我们没有野猪 没有猪肉就没有蛋白质
There's no boar. No boar, no protein.
你可以吃鱼啊 Jin捕了很多
You can eat fish. Jin's been catching a lot of 'em.
-那哥们  我欠他  -别开玩笑...
-That guy has it in for me.  -Come on...
我可不是开玩笑的 他给了我很多吃的东西  比如
I'm not kidding. He offered me some to eat, like,
在我们到这里之后
right after we, you know, got here.
嗯  那些带刺的
Um, that thing with the spikes.
海胆
Sea urchin.
是的  当我拒绝他之后
Yeah, when I turned him down,
就好象我败坏了他的家族荣誉似的
it's like I soiled his family honor or something.
从那以后他就再没正眼看过我
He hasn't looked me in the eye since.
他现在还在赌气呢
The guy holds a serious grudge.
你没打算吃那些东西吧
You're not eating those, are you?
哥们  这些不是用来吃的(用来上厕所)
Dude, these aren't for eating.
抱歉我去一下
Excuse me.
我能看到你在那
I can see you there, you know.
我并没有在藏着
I wasn't hiding.
我只是不想打断...
I just didn't want to disrupt you from doing...
你正在做的事情
...whatever it is you're doing.
这又不是什么秘密的事
It's not like it's a secret.
是你的话有时候很难说
Hard to tell with you sometimes.
啊! 恶心的小小的灰黄色的东西
Ah! Gross, little, grayish yellow things.
西番莲果的种子
Passion fruit seeds.
用来干什么的
What are they for?
想知道的话  我来告诉你
I'll show you...if you want to see.
好啊
Yeah.
跟我来
Follow me.
告诉我你发现了一个咖啡吧
Please tell me you found a coffee bar.
不是
Not quite.
你什么时候做的这些?
When did you do all this?
不是我
I didn't.
都是Sun弄的
It was all Sun.
我只是有一天无意中走到这里
I wandered into this place the other day
当时我正在采集水果
when I was picking fruit.
这真漂亮  太棒了
This is beautiful. It's great.
她种了这些草和一些比较矮的植物
She planted some herbs and some low-growing stuff here,
然后在那边建了个果树园
and then she started a grove over there.
聪明
Smart.
现在野猪没有了  我们需要
With the boar running out, we're gonna need
食物越多越好
as much food as we can possiblely get.
也许野猪并不是没有了
Maybe it's not running out.
你什么意思
What do you mean?
也许Locke并没打算继续去给我们打野猪
Maybe Locke's just decided not to catch it for us anymore.
为什么
Why would he do that?
岛上有这么多人要吃饭
A lot of mouths to feed.
如果野猪已经快没有了  他为什么要打来
If the boar's thinning out, why should he feed everyone else
给其他人吃  这样他自己不就吃不到了
at his own expense?
我们打不破玻璃
That glass isn't breaking,
门也被封死了
and the door is sealed shut.
我想它是水泥做的
I think it's cement.
那是什么?
What is that?
碗里的东西是什么
The stuff in the bowl, what is that?
一会有用的
It's for later.
也不是太难  但是...
Not to be too difficult, but...
我们到这有两天了
we've been coming here for two days,
只能盯着这东西看
just staring at this thing.
我不知道我们应该干什么
I'm not really sure what we're supposed to be doing.
Michelangelo的父亲...
Michelangelo's father
是一个很有钱的人
he was a wealthy man.
他不理解他儿子
Had no understanding of the divinity in his son,
所以他就打他儿子
so he beat him.
他的儿子中
No child of his
没有一个会用自己的双手来谋生
was gonna use his hands for a living.
所以Michelangelo也学会了不凭自己的能力做事
So Michelangelo learned not to use his hands.
几年后  一个来访问的王子
Years later, a visiting prince
来到了Michelangelo的工作室
came into Michelangelo's studio
然后发现他
and found the master
盯着一个18英尺长的大理石块
staring at a single 18-foot block of marble.
然后他就知道那些谣言是真的了
Then he knew the rumors were true that
Michelangelo每天走到这里
Michelangelo had come in every day
在过去的四个月里
for the past four months,
盯着大理石看
stared at the marble
然后就回家吃晚饭
and gone home for his supper.
所以王子就问  一个显然的问题
So the prince asked the obvious:
"你在干什么"
"What are you doing?"
然后Michelangelo就转过身来看他
And Michelangelo turned around and looked at him
轻声说
and whispered...
"我在工作"
"I'm working"
三年后  那块大理石
Three years later, that block of marble
就变成了David的雕象
was the statue of David
我们不是来这盯着它看四个月的
We're not gonna stare at this thing for four months
是不是?
are we?
我们怎么才能把它弄开
How we gonna open it?
嗯  那就是我们得解决的问题
That's what we have to figure out
就是我们得待在这里的原因
That's why we're sitting here
我是说  你怎么打开一个...
I mean, how do you open a...
没有把手或者门闩的舱门...
hatch that has no handle, no latch...
看不出能用什么方法来打开吗?
no discernible way of opening it?
谁啊
Yeah?
-我来找Shannon  -你是谁
-I'm looking for Shannon.  -Who are you?
她哥哥
I'm her brother.
Boone?
出什么事了?
What's going on?
你在这里干什么
What are you doing here?
15个小时  我刚刚在飞机上度过了15个小时
Fifteen hours. I just spent 15 hours on a plane.
"很高兴看到你"
"I'm happy to see you. Glad you're here."
说点那些话也许比较好
Something like that might work.
听着  你来的也许不是时候
Listen, this isn't really the best time.
Bryan和我正打算
Bryan and I were on our way out
去见几个朋友
to meet some friends.
你干吗不明天再给我打一个电话
Give me a call tomorrow.
求你了
Please.
好吧
Okay.
祝你玩得开心
Enjoy your friends.
Jin!
嘿  Jin
Yo, Jin!
Alto!
听我说哥们 我知道你不喜欢我
Listen I know you don't like me
因为海胆那件事情
'cause of the sea urchin thing.
没关系  我不是来找你帮忙的
That's okay, 'cause I'm not asking for any favors.
只要  告诉我你在哪里抓的鱼
Just let me know where you get the fish.
鱼
Fish.
只要告诉我大概的方向就可以了
Just point me the right direction.
我会用自己的工具去抓的
I'll take care of my own business with my own tools.
(我会用我自己的方式来管好我自己的事情)
你刚才说了些不好听的  是不是
You just said something mean, didn't you?
你知道  我们得告诉他们
You know, we're gonna have to tell 'em.
告诉他们什么?
Tell them what?
我们发现的东西
What we found.
你也知道  他们不会一直都相信
You know they're not gonna keep believing that
我们是去打猎
we're coming out here hunting.
还没到告诉他们的时候 他们不会明白的
They're not ready. They won't understand it.
-我不认为我明白  -那就是问题所在
-I don't think I understand it.  -That's the problem.
听我说  至少  我要告诉Shannon
Look, at least... I gotta tell Shannon.
这还用问吗  因为她是我妹妹
What do you mean why? 'Cause she's my sister.
为什么你这么关心她
Why do you care about her so much?
哥们你不明白的
You don't know her, man.
她非常聪明  而且在很多方面很特别
She's smart and she's special in a lot of ways.
省省吧
Fair enough.
她一直都在问我这个
She's been asking me about this.
我不能一直都对她撒谎
I can't keep lying to her.
你的意思是说你不能一直对她撒谎
You mean you can't keep lying to her,
还是你受不了她一直这样怀疑你
or you can't stand the way she makes you feel
因为你在撒谎
because you're lying to her?
都有  随便了
Both. Whatever.
听我说  她能保密的
Look, she can keep a secret.
你确定吗
You're sure?
是的  我确定
Yes, I'm sure.
不是  我是说你确定你要告诉她吗?
No. I mean, are you sure you want to do this?
我得摆脱这种处境
I gotta get her off my back.
她老是来问我这个
She keeps asking me about this,
老是来问我关于你 还有整个这件事
she keeps asking about you, about the whole thing.
你肯定你已经自己考虑过了吗?
Are you sure you've thought through the ramifications?
是的
Yes.
那么去吧
So be it.
Locke...
这是什么
What is this?
听见我说的话了吗?
you hear me?
把我解开
Untie me right now.
为什么
Or what?
我发誓我不会对任何人讲关于这个舱门的事  可以了吧
I swear I won't tell anyone about the hatch thing, okay?
我发誓
I promise.
我这样做  Boone  因为是时候让你
I'm doing this Boone, because it's time for you
让你放下一些事了
to let go of some things
因为这样对你是最好的
because it's what's best for you.
而且我保证
And I promise
以后你会因为这个感谢我的
you're gonna thank me for this later.
喂  我可不觉得这样对我来说最好的
Hey, I don't think this is best for me.
那是什么
What is that?
一个没处理的伤口...
An untreated wound out here...
会被感染的
it's gonna get infected.
你不能把我留在这儿
You're not gonna leave me here.
留不留在这取决于你
Whether you stay is up to you.
营地在西面四公里的地方
The camp is four miles due west.
西边是哪边
Which way is west?
你会自己解开的
You'll be able to cut yourself free
当你有适当的动力的时候
once you have the proper motivation.
Locke!
救命
Help!
很抱歉  Carlisle先生
I'm sorry, Mr. Carlisle,
恐怕我帮不了你
but I'm afraid I can't help you.
遗憾的是  先生 我们还得需要点东西才能继续
Unfortunately sir. We'll need a little more to go on.
我不明白  我在举报一起犯罪
I don't understand this. I'm reporting a crime.
听着  有一个精神病和她在一起 明白吗?
Look, this is a pyscho with her, okay?
我妹妹不巧被一个
My sister happens to be attracted
错误的家伙给迷住了
to the wrong kind of guy.
这是他的瓶子  我只是把它还给他
It was his bottle. I just gave it back to him.
喂  嘿  鳄鱼猎人
Hey, yo, croc hunter!
为什么都没人想听我讲啊
How come nobody wants to hear my side of the story?
如果那是她的朋友的话
Now, if that were her mate,
那我还可能帮你  知道吗
see, then I could help you.
你把要说的说完吧
Let's finish taking down rest of your information.
你刚才说她是你的妹妹
You were saying she's your sister.
那为什么她的名字是Rutherford 但你的却是Carlisle
Then why is her name Rutherford and yours Carlisle?
她结婚了没
Is she married?
她曾经结婚  现在已经离婚了
She was. She's not married anymore.
这和我们要说的没有关系
That has nothing to do with this.
Rutherford是她父亲的名字
Rutherford is her father's name.
我们父母在我10岁 她8岁的时候结婚的
Our parents married when I was 10, she was 8.
那么说她是你的继妹妹了
She's your stepsister.
是的
That's right.
没有血缘关系
No blood relation.
也许你听说过我母亲Sabrina Carlisle.
Maybe you've heard of my mother, Sabrina Carlisle.
她的婚礼生意是美国做的最大的
She owns the largest wedding business in the U.S.
我是我是经营婚礼装子公司的C.O.O.
I'm the C.O.O. of the wedding clothing subsidiary.
你想买我妻子的婚礼服吗?
Would you like to buy my wife's wedding dress?
新的要2000元  到现在为止只被穿过一次
It cost $2,000 new. It's only been worn once.
我只是想找些人去调查一下那人  仅此而已
I just want someone to go pay this guy a visit, that's all.
Carlisle先生   现在没有任何的物证
Mr Carlisle. In the absence of physical evidence
或者是直接的控告来自  呃...
or a direct complaint from...
Shannon
我们不能毫无理由的冲到别人家里面
We can't just go barging into people's apartments.
遗憾的是  我们虽然是警察  却不是管约会的警察
Sadly, we're the police, not the dating police.
Bryan  我们得谈谈
Bryan, we need to talk.
我不会浪费你的时间
I'm not gonna waste your time
我当然也不想浪费我的时间
and I'm not gonna waste mine
我要你跟我妹妹分手
I want you to break up with my sister.
什么
What?
我要你今天就结束关系  就现在
I want you to end it today. Right now.
走开  哥们
Bugger off, mate.
你不明白 你将成为第三个我必须给钱才走人的人
You don't understand. You'll be the third guy I've paid to leave.
找个她不在的时候去她家
Go to her house when she's not there
收拾好你的东西走人  再也不要跟她联系
pack your stuff and never have contact with her again.
明白了吗
Understood?
那么你大老远跑过来就是为了贿赂我啦
So you flew over here to bribe me?
我将给你25000美元
I'm going to give you 25,000 U.S. dollars.
我爱她
I love her.
多少?
How much?
你是说我对她的爱
My love for her?
至少值50000美元
It's worth closer to $50,000.
你能相信我们已经在这儿呆了三个多星期了么
Can you believe we've been here for over 3 weeks?
我本来在去Bali的路上
I was on my way to Bali.
我经常旅行
I travel a lot.
我本来正在在计划去开发那个岛
I was looking forward to exploring the island.
可是最后我坐上了去洛杉矶的飞机
Somehow I ended up on a flight to LA instead.
我想正如一句话所说
I guess that falls under the category
"小心对待你所希望的事物"
"Be careful with what you wish for"
你知道我说什么
You understood me.
你听的懂  不是吗
You did, didn't you?
你明白我说的话
You just understood what I said.
你说的是英语吗
You speak English?
求你了...
Please
不要告诉任何人
don't tell anyone.
你知道什么  好吧
You know what? Fine.
你赢了行了吧?  现在你开心了吧?
You win, okay? You happy now?
管好你的破鱼吧  我走了
Keep your damn fish. I'm outta here.
我踩到一个该死的海胆
I stepped on a friggin' urchin!
嗷  你听见没
You understand me?
你知道这会感染  组织坏死 甚至截肢吗?
You understand infection? Gangrene? Amputation?
啊  我的脚...
Ow! My foot!
嗷  你多少得做点什么
Oh. Ow! Oh, you gotta do something for me.
哥们  你最好尿在我脚上
You're gonna have to pee on my foot, man
它可以消毒  我曾在电视上看到过
It'll stop the venom. I saw it on TV.
别担心只管尿  快点
Just do it! Ow!
不  只管尿在上面  伙计 你得尿
No, just pee on it, man! You need to pee...
尿在上面
Pee on it.
尿在上面  要不然我会失去...
Pee on my foot. I'll lose...
只管尿  否则我的脚就完蛋了
Just do it. I'll lose my foot if you don't.
尿  尿在上面
pee! Just pee on it!
尿
pee!
不
No!
YYeTs美剧组
www.YYETS.com
你好
Hi.
我没听见你过来
I didn't hear you.
抱歉  尽管我自己没说过 别人都认为我是个潜行者
Sorry. I'm sneakier than I give myself credit for.
你在干什么
What are you doing out here?
我刚才在打猎  Boone认为我应该休息一下午
We were hunting. Boone thought I should take the afternoon off.
Boone在打猎吗?
Boone is hunting?
你认为你们会抓到什么吗?
You think he'll catch anything?
不
Nope.
你在这儿干什么呢  Sayid
What are you doing out here, Sayid?
野外定向
Orienteering.
我在看能不能从Rousseau的地图上找到些什么  但是...
I'm trying to make something of Rousseau's maps, but...
没什么好找的
There's nothing to make.
的确如此
Exactly.
你做了个指南针  我从没见过这东西
Well, you made a compass. I haven't seen one of those
自从我还是个weblos开始
since I was a Webelos.
weblos是什么
What's a Webelos?
介于童子军和少年军之间的东西
Halfway between a Cub Scout and a Boy Scout.
那么weblos都干些什么
And what does a Webelos do?
大多数时候  争取获得勋章
Gets badges mostly.
打绳结  给鸟类分级
Ties knots, identifies birds.
我不是个受欢迎的小孩
I wasn't the most popular kid.
这个我会留给你做
I'll leave you to it.
给
Here.
也许这个能帮上你的忙
Maybe this will help your cause.
难道你不需要吗
Don't you need this?
不再需要了
Not anymore.
来人啊  救命啊
Somebody, help me!
是谁
Who's that?
Boone?
Shannon!
我被绑起来了
I'm tied up!
什么
What?
你能过来吗?
Can you get over here?
我也被绑起来了
I'm tied up too!
Boone
坚持住  Shannon 我就来了
Hold on. Shannon I'm coming!
Boone 它越来越近了
Boone It's getting closer!
救命啊
Somebody help me!
Boone
求你了  Boone
Please, Boone!
Boone
Shannon
Boone  救救我 快点
Boone Help me! Hurry!
-我已经在努力了  -快
-I'm trying.  -Please.
求你了  快
Please hurry!
快走 快走
Go! Go!
快点
Come on!
快跑  不  不  到这里
Run! No! In here.
问个问题可以吗?
Let me ask you something.
你认为北边是哪边
Which way do you think north is?
什么
Sorry?
北边  哪个方向是北边
North. Which way is it?
好吧
Okay.
太阳在那个方向落下
The sun's gonna set there,
所以那是西方
so that makes that west.
那么哪个就是北方
That'd be north.
好
Yeah.
正确  北方应该在那
Correct. That's where north should be.
既然那是北方
Yet that is north.
我没有
I'm not...
一个微小磁场扰动
A magnetic anomaly
可能会造成2到3度的偏转
might explain a variance of two or three degrees
可是不是这样的偏转
but not this.
你什么意思
What are you saying?
我在说这个指南针有明显的错误
This compass is obviously defective.
这东西从哪来的
Where'd you get it?
今天下午Locke给我的
Locke gave it to me this afternoon.
Locke
你在哪看见Locke的
Where'd you see Locke?
离这大约一公里以东的地方
About a mile east of here
正在穿越丛林
walking through the jungle.
向东  至少我觉得是向东
East  At least I think it's east.
你对他干了什么
What did you do to him?
我对谁干了什么
What did I do to who?
Locke
你对那个神经病干了什么让他发怒的事情
What did you do to that psycho to piss him off?
我什么也没干
I didn't do anything to him.
什么  难道他这样做只是因为太无聊了吗
What, he just did it because he was bored?
-听着  我知道你们在...  -我们先回营地去
-Look, I know you guys are...  -Let's go back to camp.
你有包吗  有没有什么东西想带走的
Do you have any bags?  Anything you want to take?
不  Shannon  我们要离开这个地方
No, Shannon. we're getting out of this country.
你有什么想要带走的没有
Is there anything you want to bring with you?
你这是怎么回事
What's the matter with you?
噢  看看这
Oh, look at this.
我们走吧  求你了
Let's go, please.
快点
Come on.
我们可以走的
We can go.
嘿  兄弟  你还不明白是吧
Hey, mate, you don't get this yet, do you?
这是怎么回事
What's what.
你算计我
You set me up.
整个事情都是算计好的
This whole thing was a setup.
她只是得到她应该得到的东西
She's getting what she's owed.
你再说一遍
What did you say?
她告诉我你母亲勒索Shannon
She told me your mum screwed Shannon over
在她父亲死后
after her daddy died
把她父亲的钱全部据为己有
kept her father's money for herself.
哦  真是好妈妈  你说对了
Oh, sweet mum you got there.
这不是第一次 对吧
This isn't the first time, is it?
你以前也干过
You've done this before
你这个婊子
little bitch.
-好了  够了没有  -别碰我  你这个卑鄙的...
-That's enough.  -Don't touch me, you lowlife piece of...
Bryan  放开他
Bryan  get off of him!
放开他  放开
Get off of him! Get off!
有船吗?
Any ships?
还没有
Not yet.
可是我...有的是耐心
But I'm... patient.
不介意我也加入你们吧
Mind if I join you?
我们好久都没说过话了  John
Been a while since you and I talked, John.
嗯  你可是个大忙人
Well, you're a busy man.
你也一样
So are you.
Boone在哪
Where's Boone?
今天我还没看见过他
I haven't seen him today.
是吗?
Yeah?
你们俩整个星期都像被拴在一起一样
You two have been attached at the hip all week.
好  我来检查一下
Well, let me just check my hip.
不  Boone不在这
Nope, no Boone.
打猎打的如何了
How's the boar hunting going?
你我之间吗
Between you and me?
总是这样
Always.
恐怕它们都搬到我们的山谷外住了
I'm afraid they're beginning to migrate outside our valley.
他们真是聪明的动物
They're smart animals
聪明的动物很会适应环境
and smart animals adapt quickly
特别是当一种新的捕食者闯入了他们的环境中时
when a new predator's introduced into their environment.
你是说我们?
You mean us?
最危险的捕食者
The most dangerous predator of all.
有其他人知道吗
Does anybody else know?
只有Micheal晓得
Only Michael.
不是你丈夫么
Not your husband?
好了  我
Please...I
别担心  我会保密的
Don't worry. I can keep a secret.
我在韩国曾学过英语的
I took English lessons in Korea.
他不知道  这是...
He doesn't know. It's...
很复杂的一件事
complicated.
-那你为什么不现在告诉他呢  -我不能
-So why don't you tell him now?  -I can't.
为什么
Why?
因为我爱他
Because I love him.
我不 ...
I don't...
你曾对你爱的人撒过谎么
Have you never lied to a man you've loved?
你肯定你真的不会英语吗
You sure you don't speak English?
因为有谣言说你们会说
'Cause there's a rumor that you do.
你妻子很惹眼哪
Your wife's hot.
哦  我知道了  这算是某种回报吧
Oh, I get it. This is some kind of payback
因为上次我不愿意吃海胆吗
because I wouldn't eat the urchin the other time?
我吃这个  你给了我一条鱼  是吧
I eat this, you give me a fish, right?
好吧
Okay, fine.
嘴一闭就咽下去了
Over the lips, past the gums,
YADA,YADA...
噢  老天
Oh, God.
干杯
Cheers.
要帮忙吗?
You need a hand?
是啊
Yeah.
是的  最好有人帮个忙
I'd love one.
我看到你最近在山洞那边
I seen you around the caves lately.
我必须换个环境
I needed a change of scenery.
最近过得怎样啊  charlie
How are you doing, Charlie?
你问我我过的怎样么?
How am I doing?
是指当我对付两周的戒毒时
With week two of heroin withdrawal,
还是我处理claire被那个
or with Claire being abducted by
想杀死我的疯子绑架的事情
the freak who tried to kill me?
我给你阿斯匹林来抵抗海洛因吧  Charilie
I gave you the aspirin for the withdrawal. Charilie
你认为他的故事怎样
What do you think his story is?
谁的故事
Who?
Locke
那家伙天生就是个怪物
The guy's a freak of nature.
精神高度不正常
Highly disturbed.
他可能会把他在邮局的同事
Chances are he probably killed
都杀了
all his mates in the post office
如果他妈妈忘了在他饭盒里面放午餐甜饼
the day his mom forgot to put a cookie in his lunch.
不管怎么说  那是他留给我的第一印象
That was my first impression, anyway.
然后他就救了我的命
And then he saved my life.
那么你就信任他了么
So you trust him?
信任他
Trust him?
无意冒犯 兄弟  如果有这个岛上一个人
No offense, mate. If there's one person on this island
能让我绝对相信
I would put my absolute faith in
他能够使我们都获救 那个人就是John Locke
to save us all,  it would be John Locke.
加油  哥们    你想要那个球吗?
Come on, boy. You want the ball?
去拿那个球吧 好孩子
Go get the ball. Good boy.
兄弟  你找到自己的包了么
Dude, you found your own bag?
-这太好了  -是啊
-That's awesome, man.  -Yeah.
可以再次用你自己的牙刷真爽
Be nice to get to use your own toothbrush again.
你那有木瓜吗
Got some papaya there?
有
Yeah.
好耶
Yippee.
嘿  能不能让我  呃...
Hey, you mind if l, uh...
噢  请自便吧
Oh, knock yourself out.
你希望在你最痛恨的敌人身上发生什么事情
Want to wish something on your worst enemy?
我希望他们踩到一个海胆
Hope they step on a sea urchin.
谢谢
Thanks.
兄弟  这东西已经清理好了么
Has this already been cleaned?
你是在开玩笑吗?
Are you kidding me?
他们看来挺开心的
They look happy.
开心吗?
Happy?
把手伸出来
Put out your hand.
我保证  你会喜欢的
You'll like it, I swear.
恶心的小小的灰黄色的东西吗
Gross, little, grayish yellow things?
不  不  不  不  这些是...
No no no no no, these are...
粘稠的小小的蓝黑色的东西
slimy,little, bluish black things.
番石榴的种子
Guava seeds.
没有番石榴的花园还是花园吗?
What's a garden without guava?
你确定我们方向正确么
Are you sure we going the right direction?
如果你不想跟我走  就别跟着
If you don't want to follow, don't.
我才不会跟着你
I wouldn't have to
如果你和那个带我们到这里的疯子不是朋友的话
if you weren't best friends with that nutcase who brought us here.
你和Locke不是在打猎吧
You weren't hunting.
你们在干其他的事
You were doing something else.
我们不是已经说过这件事了吗?
Haven't we been over this?
你是个失败的骗子  Boone
You're a horrible liar. Boone
我们什么也没干
We weren't doing anything.
你为什么要为这家伙保守秘密
Why are you keeping secrets for this guy?
你知道"这个家伙"是谁吗
Do you know who "this guy" is?
他是唯一一个知道这里发生什么了的人
He's the only one here that has a clue to what's going on.
这是什么意思
What is that supposed to mean?
意思是说他很聪明
It means he's smart.
为什么呢
Why?
我们找到了些东西
We found something.
什么东西
What?
我们出去找Claire的时候
While looking for Claire
我们找到了这个...金属片
we found this... piece of metal buried in the jungle.
埋在丛林里面的  我们一直在挖它
We've been excavating.
那就是我们一直在干的事
That's what we've been doing.
在尘土下边埋着的舱门
A hatch buried in the dirt.
是的  Shannon  那个就是所谓的舱门
Yeah, Shannon  that's what a hatch is.
门里通向哪
Where does it go?
我不知道
I don't know.
但是我告诉他我想要告诉你
I told him I wanted to tell you.
然后他就对我干了这些事
That's when he did this.
快跑
Come on!
不
No!
Shannon!
Shanoon!
你想干什么
What do you want?
Bryan把钱带走了
Bryan took the money.
他跑了
He's gone.
那么杂耍演员被耍了
So the player got played.
那真有诗意  你觉得呢
That's poetic, don't you think?
我知道你一定会带钱的 我知道你会的
I knew you'd bring the money. I knew you would.
-你喝醉了  -你知道为什么吗
-You are drunk.  -Do you wanna know why?
那不重要    因为你会告诉我的
It doesn't matter, does it? Because you're going to tell me.
因为你爱上我了
Because you're in love with me.
什么
What?
你把钱带来是因为你爱上我了
You brought the money because you're in love with me.
你喝醉了出现在这里...
You show up here plastered...
你一直都爱着我
You've always been in love with me.
你一直都是一个以自我为中心的小婊子
You've always been self-centered little bitch
但现在你想错了
but now you're delusional.
我一直以来都知道
I've always known it.
你病了
You're sick.
没有...
No...
Boone
没事的
It's okay.
没关系的
Boone
我们回洛杉矶之后
When we get back to LA,
你应该告诉你母亲...
you should just tell your mom that...
你又救了我就象你从前那样
you rescued me again, just like you always do,
然后我们就可以回去
and then we'll just go back.
该去的地方
To what it was.
好像一切都是由你来决定
Like it's all up to you.
穿好衣服
Get dressed.
Shannon
不
No.
Shannon
噢  Shannon
Oh, Shannon.
它杀了她
It killed her!
可是你回来了
You made it back.
那东西杀了我妹妹
That thing killed my sister.
都是你的错   你把她带到那去的
It's your fault. You drug her out there.
-你妹妹  -不要跟我装聋作哑
-Your sister?  -Don't play dumb.
冷静一下
Calm down.
她在我怀里死去的
She died in my arms.
为什么你身上没有血迹
Why is there no blood on you?
见鬼  我刚刚在那发生了什么事
What the hell! What just happened to me out there?
我不知道
I don't know.
我不知道  你来告诉我
I don't know. You tell me.
但是你的妹妹Shannon...
But your sister, Shannon...
我是说我能够好几天都...
I mean I could spend days...
她已经死了
She... She was dead.
是不是那个东西让你看见的
Is that what it made you see?
什么东西让我看见的?
What made me see?
你放在我头上的东西
That stuff you put on my head.
你对我下了药
You drugged me?
我给你了一个我认为对于你能够在岛上
I gave you an experience that I believed was
生存下来的至关重要的经历
vital to your survival on this island.
那不是真的吗
It wasn't real?
就好象你真的经历过了一样
It was only as real as you made it.
我亲眼看见她了
I saw her.
我亲眼看见她死在我面前
I saw her die.
你有什么感觉...
How did you feel
她死的时候
when she died?
我感到 --我感到 --
I felt... I felt...
我感觉轻松了
I felt relieved.
是的
Yes.
该放下这些事了
Time to let go.
跟我来
Follow me.
==============|  YYeTs字幕组招募启示  |==============
英文字幕录制(居住在加拿大和美国)  双语字幕校正   时间轴调整
英语翻译   欧美影视新闻翻译  影视评论  论坛版主  美工人员
服务器提供者  发布宣传  联系地址：www.YYeTs.com
==== YYeTs属于网络爱好者组织 加入者仅凭个人兴趣爱好 无报酬 ====